const questions = [
  { 
    id: 1,
    question: 'Kamusta ka?',
    choices: ['Who are you?', 'How are you?', 'Where are you?'],
    correctAnswer: 'How are you?'
  },
  { 
    id: 2,
    question: 'Magandang umaga!',
    choices: ['Good Afternoon!', 'Good Evening!', 'Good Morning!'],
    correctAnswer: 'Good Morning!'
  },
  { 
    id: 3,
    question: 'Maraming salamat sayo',
    choices: ['Let\'s eat', 'Thank you very much', 'Let\'s go'],
    correctAnswer: 'Thank you very much'
  },
  { 
    id: 4,
    question: 'Kumain na ba kayo?',
    choices: ['Have you eaten?', 'Have you slept?', 'Have you drank?'],
    correctAnswer: 'Have you eaten?'
  },
  { 
    id: 5,
    question: 'Anong oras na?',
    choices: ['What time is it?', 'How much is it?', 'Can we go?'],
    correctAnswer: 'What time is it?'
  },
  { 
    id: 6,
    question: 'Ano ang pagkain natin?',
    choices: ['What is your hobby?', 'What is the color?', 'What is our food?'],
    correctAnswer: 'What is our food?'
  },
  { 
    id: 7,
    question: 'Ano ang pangalan mo?',
    choices: ['What is your name?', 'What is her name?', 'What is their name?'],
    correctAnswer: 'What is your name?'
  },
  { 
    id: 8,
    question: 'Saan ang bahay mo?',
    choices: ['Where is your house?', 'Where is your kitchen?', 'Where is your garden?'],
    correctAnswer: 'Where is your house?'
  },
  { 
    id: 9,
    question: 'Mahilig ka ba sa mga hayop?',
    choices: ['Where is the toilet?', 'How is the weather?', 'Do you like animals?'],
    correctAnswer: 'Do you like animals?'
  },
  { 
    id: 10,
    question: 'Mahal kita',
    choices: ['It\'s expensive', 'It\'s not enough', 'I love you'],
    correctAnswer: 'I love you'
  },
  { 
    id: 11,
    question: 'Pwede mo ba akong tulungan?',
    choices: ['Can you help me?', 'Can we go out?', 'Can we go to lunch?'],
    correctAnswer: 'Can you help me?'
  },
  { 
    id: 12,
    question: 'Paumanhin po, nanay.',
    choices: ['I love you, mom', 'I\'m sorry, mom', 'See you later, mom'],
    correctAnswer: 'I\'m sorry, mom'
  },
  { 
    id: 13,
    question: 'Nagugutom ka na ba?',
    choices: ['Are you mad at me?', 'Are you hungry?', 'Are you thirsty?'],
    correctAnswer: 'Are you hungry?'
  },
  { 
    id: 14,
    question: 'Nasaan ang banyo ninyo?',
    choices: ['Where are your keys?', 'Where is your room?', 'Where is your bathroom?'],
    correctAnswer: 'Where is your bathroom?'
  },
  { 
    id: 15,
    question: 'Mahilig ka ba sa aso o sa pusa?',
    choices: ['Do you like dogs or cats?', 'Do you like birds or fish?', 'Do you like rabbits or cats?'],
    correctAnswer: 'Do you like dogs or cats?'
  }
]

export default questions